Track 3.2 Unit 3 Grammar Activity 1
Bài 3.2 Bài 3 Ngữ pháp Hoạt động 1
Listen and circle
Nghe và khoanh tròn
I'm really happy today because I'm at the park.
Hôm nay mình rất vui vì mình ở công viên.
My friend Jacob is at the park with me too.
Bạn Jacob của mình cũng ở công viên với mình.
Jacob is sad because his ball is in the tree.
Jacob buồn vì quả bóng của cậu ấy bị mắc trên cây.
Lily is 9 today. Her birthday party was yesterday. It was very loud.
Hôm nay Lily 9 tuổi. Tiệc sinh nhật của bạn ấy là hôm qua. Rất ồn ào.
It's sunny and warm today, but it was cold yesterday.
Hôm nay trời nắng và ấm, nhưng hôm qua trời lạnh.
Yesterday I was at school, but today I'm at the beach with my family.
Hôm qua mình ở trường, nhưng hôm nay mình ở bãi biển với gia đình.
Last week I was sad because my grandma was in hospital. Today I'm happy because she is at home.
Tuần trước mình buồn vì bà mình nằm viện. Hôm nay mình vui vì bà đã về nhà.
Sylvia and Rosa are tired today because they were at the cinema last night.
Sylvia và Rosa hôm nay mệt vì tối qua họ ở rạp chiếu phim.